[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The islanders initially formed a monarchy to resolve disputes.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The senator-in-chief had executive authority in the newly formed government.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "The government’s primary function was to oversee private businesses and individual savings.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "The constitution was designed to limit government power and protect individual liberties.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "The formation of the Republic of Usonia mirrored the establishment of the United States.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Taxes were introduced to fund military expenses, but not for infrastructure projects.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The Republic of Usonia was founded as a monarchy with a central ruler.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The creation of lighthouses was one of the measures taken to protect commerce.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "The government’s role was seen as necessary for the protection and economic stability of the island.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "The islanders viewed excessive taxation as a positive way to boost private savings.",
      "Answer": "False"
    }
  ]
  